<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hobbies on Terminal</title>
    <link>/myportfolio/hobbies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hobbies on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 20:17:04 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/myportfolio/hobbies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>movieWatchList</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/hobbies/moviewatchlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 20:17:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/hobbies/moviewatchlist/</guid>
      <description>Intro I have absolutely loved film ever since I made friends with Ethan M. in high school. He exposed me to all sorts of fantastic movies and opened my eyes to the awesome potential the cinema has for art and storytelling. Since high school I have delved deeper and deeper into my love of film by taking film classes and watching movies often. I always have an ongoing watch list (see below) of movies, but it has always been my preference to see movies in theaters.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have absolutely loved film ever since I made friends with Ethan M. in high school. He exposed me to all sorts of fantastic movies and opened my eyes to the awesome potential the cinema has for art and storytelling. Since high school I have delved deeper and deeper into my love of film by taking film classes and watching movies often. I always have an ongoing watch list (see below) of movies, but it has always been my preference to see movies in theaters. On this page I will keep my watch list as well as keep track of movies I have seen in theaters that were exceptional. I hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;favorite-theater-viewings&#34;&gt;Favorite Theater Viewings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally think there are some movies that can only be fully enjoyed when seen in theaters &amp;ndash; &lt;em&gt;Pacific Rim&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Saving Private Ryan&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt;, etc. The movie theater is the original medium of film and immerses the audience unlike any home theater could with the larger-than-life screen and the seat shaking speakers. Since many people would disagree with me on this, I have decided to compile a list of the movies I have seen in theaters that I felt were &lt;em&gt;enhanced&lt;/em&gt; by the venue itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;9302021---akira&#34;&gt;9/30/2021 - Akira&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Akira at the time of its release (1988) had the highest budget of any animated movie up until that point, and it shows. Entirely hand drawn, the film has a run time of 124 minutes which required over an estimated 160,000 individual drawings. This makes for a wonderfully fluid and smooth viewing experience which became the inspiration for an entire generation of Japanese media.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/movieWatchList/akira.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The movie takes you through a Neo-Tokyo cityscape plagued by corruption, gang violence, and terrorism as the main character, Kaneda, searches for his abducted friend Tetsuo. From the action shots to the world building, the animation is breathtaking and easily surpasses many of its modern copy-cats. The soundtrack is still infamous for its eerie undertones and perfectly sets the mood. But, don&amp;rsquo;t take my word for it, watch the introduction for yourself! (there are English captions)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Avnq3rFnezE&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, enough gushing. I had the opportunity to see the remastered &lt;em&gt;Akira&lt;/em&gt; with its original audio in theaters while at school and I eagerly jumped at the chance. I went with several of my friends (some seeing it for the first time) and we all walked out as if in a daze &amp;ndash; it was awesome! If you ever get the chance to see it in theaters DO SO! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to see it yet, WATCH IT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: Only watch &lt;em&gt;Akira&lt;/em&gt; if you can see it in its original audio version with subtitles; the &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/ve-SiqRYLXM&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;English dub is absolutely terrible&lt;/a&gt;
 and breaks the spell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;10282021---dune&#34;&gt;10/28/2021 - Dune&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon after its release, I made a point of making a trip to a movie theater to see some sandworms on the big screen. I read &lt;em&gt;Dune&lt;/em&gt; over quarantine in 2020 and absolutely loved it, prompting me to read the next 3 books in the series. When I heard there was a movie coming out, and directed by Denis Villeneuve nonetheless, I could barely contain my excitement. However, I had been disappointed by movies portrayals of books before so I tried to temper my enthusiasm&amp;hellip; but I was almost entirely unsuccessful.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/movieWatchList/dune.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, there was no need to curb my enthusiasm because &lt;em&gt;Dune&lt;/em&gt; exceeded my expectations in terms of cinematic aesthetic while still adhering strongly to the book&amp;rsquo;s plot. I thought the soundtrack was wonderfully fitting and the entire atmosphere of the movie practically screamed &amp;ldquo;Arrakis!&amp;rdquo;. Cinematically the world building was wonderful and the culture and technology on display carried an undeniable &lt;em&gt;weight&lt;/em&gt; to it &amp;ndash; I should have expected no less of the director of &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The big screen only helped to enhance the beautiful landscapes and civilizations built within the camera&amp;rsquo;s lens. I think I will be making a return trip to the theater soon before it&amp;rsquo;s too late to see it again&amp;hellip; maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll do IMAX this time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-watch-list&#34;&gt;My Watch List&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Genre&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Amadeus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Come and See&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dallas Buyers Club&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Do the Right Thing&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, Comedy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Driveways&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Knife in the Water&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Green Mile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;A Promising Young Woman&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Girl with the Dragon Tattoo&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense, Mystery&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Assistant&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Gift&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Touching the Void&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;A Ghost Story&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Moonstruck&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Witness&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance, Crime&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Upgrade&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Action&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chronicle&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Action&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;High Life&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sputnik&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tenet&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Road&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Post Apocalyptic&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dr. Stangelove&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Comedy, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Napoleon Dynamite&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Comedy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Citizen 4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Crumb&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Last Breath&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;This is What Winning Looks Like&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Jarhead&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Schindler&amp;rsquo;s List&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Deer Hunter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Manchurian Candidate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Clue (1985)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Mystery&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Winter Bones&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Mystery, Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Rango&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Western&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Blue Velvet&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Thriller&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
