<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hobbies on Terminal</title>
    <link>/myportfolio/hobbies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hobbies on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 12:34:39 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/myportfolio/hobbies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>weightLifting</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/hobbies/weightlifting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 12:34:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/hobbies/weightlifting/</guid>
      <description>Intro Physical fitness is extremely important to me. Without constant exercise, I start to go stir crazy and get super irritable. This was never a problem in high school when I was playing a variety of sports and had daily practices, but since starting college I needed to find a new outlet. Several of my close friends in high school took up weightlifting and they introduced me to it the summer after my Freshman year &amp;ndash; I quickly took to it and dived in head first after two semesters of restlessness.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Physical fitness is &lt;strong&gt;extremely&lt;/strong&gt; important to me. Without constant exercise, I start to go stir crazy and get super irritable. This was never a problem in high school when I was playing  a variety of sports and had daily practices, but since starting college I needed to find a new outlet. Several of my close friends in high school took up weightlifting and they introduced me to it the summer after my Freshman year &amp;ndash; I quickly took to it and dived in head first after two semesters of restlessness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lifting appeals to me greatly because it is very &lt;strong&gt;flexible&lt;/strong&gt;. Depending on what else I have going on in my life, I can make lifting as &lt;strong&gt;rigorous or relaxed&lt;/strong&gt; as I like. It also has tons of variation, so I&amp;rsquo;ll never get bored with it. If I get tired of certain exercises I&amp;rsquo;ll just write a new split and start working on other stuff!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;empirical nature&lt;/strong&gt; of it also appeals to me &amp;ndash; it is extremely easy to measure and track progress which makes setting goals easy. I joke sometimes that &lt;strong&gt;lifting is like real life Runescape&lt;/strong&gt;, but instead of getting experience for a profession you&amp;rsquo;re just getting a higher max score for certain lifts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;diet&#34;&gt;Diet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have learned that diet is the most important thing when lifting &lt;em&gt;BY FAR&lt;/em&gt;. I would go so far as to say 80% diet : 20 % working out. This is because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter what you&amp;rsquo;re doing in the gym &amp;ndash; if you aren&amp;rsquo;t eating right, you won&amp;rsquo;t build muscle. Without fuel, your body simply can&amp;rsquo;t build muscle or replenish itself!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a tough lesson for me to learn since I have had a problem with under-eating since I was a kid. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until I started forcing myself to eat more that I finally started to see rapid progress towards my goals in the gym. It took me a while to figure out how much my body needed, but I now know my body&amp;rsquo;s baseline is ~1670-1700 daily calories to maintain my current weight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When attempting to gain muscle, you &lt;em&gt;MUST&lt;/em&gt; hit your body&amp;rsquo;s baseline calorie count each day. The fact of the matter is, it&amp;rsquo;s impossible to gain &lt;em&gt;ANYTHING &amp;ndash; fat or muscle&lt;/em&gt; unless you are eating a caloric surplus. Generally, it is recommended you try to eat a surplus of 500 calories on exercise days if you want to gain ~1 lb per week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-current-split&#34;&gt;My Current Split&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the 2021 fall semester I have had a lot of time to focus on lifting due to my academic load being relatively light. As a result, I have taken this opportunity to put on as much muscle as possible before I get busy again. This is because it is relatively easy to maintain muscle mass compared to building it (since building muscle requires higher regularity of eating and exercising).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This semester I have had the ambitious goal of exercising 6 days a week, and eating 2200+ calories each day. This dietary part has been by far the more difficult of the two since I have such a bad habit of under eating. However, I have been able to put together weekly meals that help me reach my caloric goal. I have also set numeric goals for my sets in the gym:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comfortable 5x5 Weight:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bench Press: 185&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Squat: 225&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dead Lift: 225&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;split&#34;&gt;Split&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goals:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen chest and increase bench press weight.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5x5 @ 185, 3x2 @ 225&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build up core strength&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain barbell squat and practice technique&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6 Day Split: Push -&amp;gt; Pull -&amp;gt; Legs -&amp;gt; Push -&amp;gt; Pull -&amp;gt; Core&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Day&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Week Day&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Schedule&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Duration&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Push A&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Monday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Barbell Bench Press&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;1x Warmup, 2x 5-8 Heavy, 3x 10-12 Moderate&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Chest Fly x Tricep Extension (Super Set)&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12, 4x 7-10&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Lateral Dumbbell Raise&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Shrugs&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Dips&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x AMRAP&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Pull A&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tuesday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Pull up&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x Warm up&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Hammer Curl&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Reverse Grip Rows&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Cable Curls&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Cable Rows&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x 20 Drop Set&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;6) Dumbbell Curls&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;1x Triple Drop Set&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Legs&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Wednesday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Box Jumps&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x Warm up&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Barbell Back Squat&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x Warm up, 4x 8-12 Heavy, 1x AMRAP Moderate&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Barbell Standing Calf Raise&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12 (then paritals until failure)&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Hip Thrusts&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Quad Extensions&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x 10-12, 2x Triple Drop Set&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;90m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Push B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Thursday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Standing Overhead Barbell Press&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Incline Dumbbell Press x Push up (Super Set)&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Overhead Tricep Extension&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Cable or Machine Fly&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Dips&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x AMRAP&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Pull B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Friday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Lat Pulldown&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x Warm up, 3x 8-10 Drop set&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Dumbbell Row&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x Warm up, 2x 6-8 Heavy, 1x 10-12 Moderate&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Incline Seated Dumbbell Curls&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Pull Up&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x AMRAP&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Reverse EZ Bar Curl&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x 8-10, 2x 40 seconds&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Core&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Saturday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Medicine Ball Twist&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 20&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Crunches w Twist&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 20&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Ab Roll-out x Hanging Knee Raises (Super Set)&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 15&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Good Morning&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;5x 15&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Plank&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;1x Through the Fire and the Flames track&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;REST&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sunday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Yoga/Stretching&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>movieWatchList</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/hobbies/moviewatchlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 20:17:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/hobbies/moviewatchlist/</guid>
      <description>Intro I have absolutely loved film ever since I met my friend Ethan M. in high school. He exposed me to all sorts of fantastic movies and opened my eyes to the awesome potential the cinema has for art and storytelling. Since high school I have delved deeper into my love of film by taking film classes and watching movies often. I always have an ongoing watch list (see below) of movies, but it has always been my preference to see movies in theaters.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have absolutely loved film ever since I met my friend Ethan M. in high school. He exposed me to all sorts of fantastic movies and opened my eyes to the awesome potential the cinema has for art and storytelling. Since high school I have delved deeper into my love of film by taking film classes and watching movies often. I always have an ongoing watch list (see below) of movies, but it has always been my preference to see movies in theaters. On this page I will keep my watch list as well as keep track of movies I have seen in theaters that were exceptional. I hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;favorite-theater-viewings&#34;&gt;Favorite Theater Viewings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally think there are some movies that can only be fully enjoyed when seen in theaters &amp;ndash; &lt;em&gt;Pacific Rim&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Saving Private Ryan&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt;, etc. The movie theater is the original medium of film and immerses the audience unlike any home theater could with the larger-than-life screen and the seat shaking speakers. Since some people might disagree with me on this, I have decided to compile a list of the movies I have seen in theaters that I felt were &lt;em&gt;enhanced&lt;/em&gt; by the venue itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;9302021---akira&#34;&gt;9/30/2021 - Akira&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Akira at the time of its release (1988) had the highest budget of any animated movie up until that point, and it shows. Entirely hand-drawn, the film has a run time of 124 minutes which required over an estimated 160,000 individual drawings. This makes for a wonderfully fluid and smooth viewing experience which became the inspiration for an entire generation of Japanese media.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/movieWatchList/akira.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The movie takes you through a Neo-Tokyo cityscape plagued by corruption, gang violence, and terrorism as the main character, Kaneda, searches for his abducted friend Tetsuo. From the action shots to the world building, the animation is breathtaking and easily surpasses many of its modern copy-cats. The soundtrack is still infamous for its eerie undertones and perfectly sets the mood. But don&amp;rsquo;t take my word for it, watch the introduction for yourself! (there are English captions)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Avnq3rFnezE&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, enough gushing. I had the opportunity to see the remastered &lt;em&gt;Akira&lt;/em&gt; with its original audio in theaters while at school and I eagerly jumped at the chance. I went with several of my friends (some seeing it for the first time) and we all walked out as if in a daze &amp;ndash; it was awesome! If you ever get the chance to see it in theaters DO SO! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to see it yet, WATCH IT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: Only watch &lt;em&gt;Akira&lt;/em&gt; if you can see it in its original audio version with subtitles; the &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/ve-SiqRYLXM&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;English dub is absolutely terrible&lt;/a&gt;
 and breaks the spell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;10282021---dune&#34;&gt;10/28/2021 - Dune&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon after its release, I made a point of making a trip to a movie theater to see some sandworms on the big screen. I read &lt;em&gt;Dune&lt;/em&gt; over quarantine in 2020 and absolutely loved it, prompting me to read the next 3 books in the series. When I heard there was a movie coming out, and directed by Denis Villeneuve nonetheless, I could barely contain my excitement. However, I had been disappointed by movies portrayals of books before, so I tried to temper my enthusiasm&amp;hellip; but I was almost entirely unsuccessful.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/movieWatchList/dune.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, there was no need to curb my enthusiasm because &lt;em&gt;Dune&lt;/em&gt; exceeded my expectations in terms of cinematic aesthetic while still adhering strongly to the book&amp;rsquo;s plot. I thought the soundtrack was wonderfully fitting and the entire atmosphere of the movie practically screamed &amp;ldquo;Arrakis!&amp;rdquo;. Cinematically the world building was wonderful and the culture and technology on display carried an undeniable &lt;em&gt;weight&lt;/em&gt; to it &amp;ndash; I should have expected no less from the director of &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The big screen only helped to enhance the beautiful landscapes and civilizations built within the camera&amp;rsquo;s lens. I think I will be making a return trip to the theater soon before it&amp;rsquo;s too late to see it again&amp;hellip; maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll do IMAX this time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-watch-list&#34;&gt;My Watch List&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Genre&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Amadeus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Come and See&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dallas Buyers Club&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Do the Right Thing&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, Comedy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Driveways&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Knife in the Water&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Green Mile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;A Promising Young Woman&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Girl with the Dragon Tattoo&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense, Mystery&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Assistant&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Gift&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Touching the Void&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;A Ghost Story&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Moonstruck&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Witness&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance, Crime&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Upgrade&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Action&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chronicle&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Action&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;High Life&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sputnik&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tenet&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Road&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Post Apocalyptic&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dr. Stangelove&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Comedy, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Napoleon Dynamite&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Comedy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Citizen 4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Crumb&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Last Breath&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;This is What Winning Looks Like&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Jarhead&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Schindler&amp;rsquo;s List&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Deer Hunter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Manchurian Candidate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Clue (1985)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Mystery&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Winter Bones&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Mystery, Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Rango&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Western&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Blue Velvet&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Thriller&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
