<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>softDevInternships on Terminal</title>
    <link>/workxp/softdevinternships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in softDevInternships on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 15:47:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/workxp/softdevinternships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>/workxp/softdevinternships/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 15:25:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workxp/softdevinternships/sap/</guid>
      <description>Intro In April 2020 I accepted a summer internship with SAP. I had a wonderful time working with a team of extremely talented developers. The experience helped me grow as a professional and taught me many valuable technical skills!
The following summer I was given a return offer to intern with the same team at SAP and I jumped at the opportunity. My second internship with SAP was just as rewarding and I was able to build off the things I had learned the previous year.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In April 2020 I accepted a summer internship with &lt;strong&gt;SAP&lt;/strong&gt;. I had a wonderful time working with a team of extremely talented developers. The experience helped me grow as a professional and taught me many valuable technical skills!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following summer I was given a return offer to intern with the same team at SAP and I jumped at the opportunity. My second internship with SAP was just as rewarding and I was able to build off the things I had learned the previous year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;meet-the-team&#34;&gt;Meet the Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was part of the &amp;ldquo;K-Force&amp;rdquo; team working on SAP&amp;rsquo;s Learning Management Suite (LMS) as an intern. Below is a picture of all of us at a company lunch from June 2021!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;/img/workXp/sapTeam.png&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;(From left to right) Birla, Bhargavi, Krupali, Sarath, Shweta, Divya, Shiva, and Me&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Krupali&lt;/strong&gt; is the &lt;strong&gt;team lead&lt;/strong&gt; for K-Force and she is AWESOME! Not only is she a talented developer, she is also an excellent communicator and it was an absolute pleasure to work under her leadership.
&lt;strong&gt;Sarath and Shiva&lt;/strong&gt; were my &lt;strong&gt;mentors&lt;/strong&gt; who I was extremely thankful for. They are both kind and capable; they are also infinitely patient and were always willing to answer my questions when I inevitably got stuck.
&lt;strong&gt;Birla&lt;/strong&gt; is K-Force&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;lead architect&lt;/strong&gt; making him responsible for code reviews. He has an incredibly deep understanding of SAP&amp;rsquo;s enormous code base&amp;hellip; and a great sense of humor. All of K-Force&amp;rsquo;s pull requests had to go through him for review and he would check that the code changes followed the conventions and standards of SAP&amp;rsquo;s code base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team as a whole was extraordinary. Everyone was so friendly and talented; it was a pleasure to work with them. I am so thankful to all of K-Force for being so welcoming and helpful, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have asked for a better team!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-contributions&#34;&gt;My Contributions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made improvements to SAP&amp;rsquo;s LMS that are now &lt;strong&gt;live&lt;/strong&gt; on the most recent version of their software! But first, &lt;strong&gt;what is LMS&lt;/strong&gt;? LMS is like a &lt;strong&gt;professional version of BlackBoard or Canvas&lt;/strong&gt;; it is an all-in-one application for assigning, taking, and completing online learning courses such as certifications, on-boarding education, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my features displayed specific information for a given class, such as &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;How to Avoid Phishing Attacks&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;. The implementation required that I &lt;strong&gt;pass information&lt;/strong&gt; pertaining to the class to a database and &lt;strong&gt;use it to query&lt;/strong&gt; for the relevant table information to be displayed. The query results then needed to be &lt;strong&gt;converted into Java objects&lt;/strong&gt; before being passed back to the point of request to be displayed. This may seem like a relatively simple process &amp;ndash; use local variables to query a database and return the results, right?&lt;br&gt;
Well you would be correct if the SAP code base wasn&amp;rsquo;t &lt;strong&gt;hundreds of thousands of lines long&lt;/strong&gt;. To access the database, I needed to pass the information through both the &lt;strong&gt;data and business layer of the application&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; a process that involved a number of existing and new Java objects. Here is the API diagram I made for my requirement to give you an idea of complexity of the code base I had to navigate:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/workXp/api.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hardest part when implementing my features was simply &lt;strong&gt;understanding&lt;/strong&gt; the existing code &amp;ndash; it was just so overwhelming at first! I spent hours parsing and tracing the codebase until I had an inkling of the existing mechanisms. Once my research was complete, I would propose a solution to Krupali and Birla, and with their go-ahead I would start implementation! I repeated this process numerous times throughout my internships which has given me a lot of confidence in my ability to understand complex code bases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned&#34;&gt;Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learned so much from my time at SAP, but one of the most important lessons I took away from the experience was the importance of &lt;strong&gt;asking for help&lt;/strong&gt;. When I first started, I was terribly nervous to ask anyone for help understanding the code base because I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to look stupid. Looking back, that was silly and I wish it hadn&amp;rsquo;t slowed me down as much as it did.
Thankfully, I had amazing mentors who quickly made it clear to me that it was OK to be confused and ask questions. They were extremely sympathetic to my struggle and were always happy to explain parts of the code that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t wrap my head around. This made me realize that being confused was just a part of the job which gave me a huge boost in confidence. I will no longer be worried about seeming foolish when asking questions &amp;ndash; sometimes, you just need some help.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>solutionStreet</title>
      <link>/workxp/softdevinternships/solutionstreet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 15:47:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workxp/softdevinternships/solutionstreet/</guid>
      <description>Intro Following my Freshman year at Case Western Reserve University, I was hired as an intern for Solution Street, a local software development company. At Solution Street I had the opportunity to work with a team composed of interns (except for our team lead) on an entirely new project! This presented a unique learning opportunity and taught me so much more about software development beyond the technical details.
As a team, we were tasked with creating a new web-based application for a local catering company &amp;ndash; Smokin&#39; Willy&amp;rsquo;s BBQ!</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following my Freshman year at Case Western Reserve University, I was hired as an intern for Solution Street, a local software development company. At Solution Street I had the opportunity to work with a team &lt;strong&gt;composed of interns&lt;/strong&gt; (except for our team lead) on an &lt;strong&gt;entirely new project&lt;/strong&gt;! This presented a unique learning opportunity and taught me so much more about software development beyond the technical details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a team, we were tasked with creating a new web-based application for a local catering company &amp;ndash; Smokin&#39; Willy&amp;rsquo;s BBQ! The owner of Smokin&#39; Willy&amp;rsquo;s was having trouble managing an increasing number of orders and came to Solution Street looking for a &lt;strong&gt;business solution&lt;/strong&gt;. A deal was struck between the two and a team of 4 interns and 1 part-time employee got to work on an application in exchange for free catering at future company picnics!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;meet-the-team&#34;&gt;Meet the Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I worked with 3 other interns at Solution Street named Greg, Mark, and Adam. We were led by a part time employee named &lt;strong&gt;Olga Lorenz&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; she&amp;rsquo;s awesome. The 5 of us all reported to &lt;strong&gt;Arthur Frankel&lt;/strong&gt;, a co-founder of Solution Street (and the guy in charge of hiring us).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Arthur&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Olga&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/workXp/arthur.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/workXp/olga.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Co-founder of Solution Street, and who hired me!&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;My team leader&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-contributions&#34;&gt;My Contributions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a team, we sat down &lt;strong&gt;with the owner&lt;/strong&gt; of Smokin&#39; Willy&amp;rsquo;s (William himself!) and worked with him to understand his business practices and what we could do to make &lt;strong&gt;running his business easier&lt;/strong&gt;. Olga would lead these meetings, but all of us made suggestions and contributed to the discussion on what we could build for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once we had an idea of how his business worked, we got to work on development. We followed an &lt;strong&gt;Agile&lt;/strong&gt; development cycle which consisted of daily scrum meetings and weekly sprint meetings &amp;ndash; which William was present for. We used &lt;strong&gt;Unfuddle&lt;/strong&gt; as our ticketing system, and under Olga&amp;rsquo;s guidance we began to build the web application using a &lt;strong&gt;Ruby on Rails&lt;/strong&gt; back-end and an &lt;strong&gt;HTML/CSS&lt;/strong&gt; front end. We often worked together on the same tickets since we were all seated next to each other in the office, and we made code peer reviews a normal practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a developer I worked on a number of different parts of the web application, both front-end and back-end. One of the features I am most proud of is a calendar embedded in the home page of the website. This calendar was dynamic and would automatically be populated with orders as they came in through the website! When clicked on, events could be added to the calendar and existing events could be expanded or modified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned&#34;&gt;Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since Solution Street was my first serious software development experience, I learned a ton about the development process and technology. It was my first exposure to an agile development cycle and a full stack framework such as Ruby on Rails. This helped me become a much more technically proficient candidate for future internship positions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond the technical side of software development, however, I also learned about the business side. Being able to sit down and &lt;strong&gt;talk face-to-face with a client&lt;/strong&gt; was an extremely rewarding experience and it greatly expanded my understanding of how software development companies do business. Something that struck me was the &lt;strong&gt;importance of communication&lt;/strong&gt; between the developers and the client, and how there can often be a bit of a &amp;ldquo;language barrier&amp;rdquo; between the two. For instance, William was an excellent chef, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t know anything about software; it became our job as representatives of Solution Street to &lt;strong&gt;help him understand the potential of our application&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way we did this was by first asking him to explain to us his normal business process for taking and filling orders. This gave us a general picture for what kind of application to make. Then, we asked that he identify the steps in his business process that took the most time and together we discussed how we could build off the current application to &lt;strong&gt;automate those time-consuming steps&lt;/strong&gt;. Sitting down and working with a client taught me so much about software development that I had never considered before and encouraged me to view the industry more from the view of the consumer than the producer.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
