<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terminal</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 15:47:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAP</title>
      <link>/workxp/softdevinternships/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 15:25:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workxp/softdevinternships/sap/</guid>
      <description>Intro In April of 2020 I accepted a summer internship with SAP. That summer I had a wonderful time working with a team of extremely talented developers. The experience helped me grow as a professional and taught me many valuable technical skills!
The following summer I was given a return offer to intern with the same team at SAP again and I jumped at the opportunity. My second internship with SAP was just as rewarding and I was able to build off of the things I had learned the previous year.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In April of 2020 I accepted a summer internship with SAP. That summer I had a wonderful time working with a team of extremely talented developers. The experience helped me grow as a professional and taught me many valuable technical skills!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following summer I was given a return offer to intern with the same team at SAP again and I jumped at the opportunity. My second internship with SAP was just as rewarding and I was able to build off of the things I had learned the previous year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;meet-the-team&#34;&gt;Meet the Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was part of the &amp;ldquo;K-Force&amp;rdquo; team working on SAP&amp;rsquo;s Learning Management Suite (LMS) as an intern. Below is a picture of all of us at a company lunch from June 2021!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;/img/workXp/sapTeam.png&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;(From left to right) Birla, Bhargavi, Krupali, Sarath, Shweta, Divya, Shiva, and Me&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Krupali is the team lead for K-Force and she is AWESOME! Not only is she a talented developer, she is also an excellent communicator and it was an absolute to work under her leadership.
Sarath and Shiva were my mentors and I am extremely thankful for them. They are both kind and capable; they are also infinitely patient and were always willing to answer my questions when I inevitably got stuck.
Birla is K-Force&amp;rsquo;s lead architect making him responsible for code reviews. He has an incredibly deep understanding of SAP&amp;rsquo;s enormous code base&amp;hellip; and a great sense of humor. All of K-Force&amp;rsquo;s pull requests had to go through him for review and he would check that the code changes followed the conventions and standards of SAP&amp;rsquo;s code base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team as a whole was extraordinary. Everyone was so friendly and talented; it was a pleasure to work with them. I am so thankful to all of K-Force for being so welcoming and helpful, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have asked for a better team!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-contributions&#34;&gt;My Contributions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made improvements to SAP&amp;rsquo;s LMS that are now live on the most recent version of their software! But first, what is LMS? LMS is like a professional version of BlackBoard or Canvas; it is an all in one application for assigning, taking, and completing online learning courses such as certifications, on-boarding education, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my features displayed specific information for a given class, such as &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;How to Avoid Phishing Attacks&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;. The implementation required that I pass information pertaining to the class to a database and use it to query for the relevant table information to be displayed. The query results then needed to be converted into java objects before being passed back to the point of request to be displayed. This may seem like a relatively simple process &amp;ndash; use local variables to query a database and return the results, right?&lt;br&gt;
Well you would be correct if the SAP code base wasn&amp;rsquo;t hundred of thousands of lines long. To access the database, I needed to pass the information through both the data and business layer of the application &amp;ndash; a process that involved a number of existing and new Java objects. Here is the API diagram I made for my requirement to give you an idea of complexity of the code base I had to navigate:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/workXp/api.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hardest part when implementing my features was simply understanding the existing code &amp;ndash; it was just so overwhelming at first! I spent hours and hours parsing and tracing the codebase until I had an inkling of the existing mechanisms. Once my research was complete, I would propose a solution to Krupali and Birla, and with their go-ahead I would start implementation! I repeated this process numerous times throughout my internships which has given me a lot of confidence in my ability to understand complex code bases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned&#34;&gt;Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learned so much from my time at SAP, but one of the most important lessons I took away from the experience was the importance of asking for help. When I first started I was terribly nervous to ask anyone for help understanding the code base because I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to look stupid. Looking back, that was a silly way to think and I wish it hadn&amp;rsquo;t slowed me down as much as it did.
Thankfully, I had amazing mentors who quickly made it clear to me that it was OK to be confused and ask questions. The were extremely sympathetic to my struggle and were always happy to explain parts of the code that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t wrap my head around. This made me realize that being confused was just a part of the job which gave me a huge boost in confidence. I will no longer be worried about seeming foolish when asking questions &amp;ndash; sometimes, you just need some help!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>casePlace</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/schoolwork/caseplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 13:31:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/schoolwork/caseplace/</guid>
      <description>Intro Here is a link to our website!
CasePlace is oriented towards prospective and current students of Case Western Reserve University (CWRU) as well as any parents or guests visiting the campus. Its purpose is to make our urban campus easier to navigate by offering an interactive GoogleMap interface with pre-loaded points of interest.
CasePlace is a web application that 5 peers and myself worked together to create for our Senior Project.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://case-place-5t56t.ondigitalocean.app&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;
 to our website!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CasePlace is oriented towards prospective and current students of Case Western Reserve University (CWRU) as well as any parents or guests visiting the campus. Its purpose is to make our urban campus easier to navigate by offering an interactive GoogleMap interface with pre-loaded points of interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CasePlace is a web application that 5 peers and myself worked together to create for our Senior Project. We built this application using React (so it even works on mobile) and it utilizes the GoogleMaps API to make an interactive map of our university&amp;rsquo;s campus! It was inspired by an &lt;a href=&#34;https://webapps.case.edu/map/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;existing web-page that CWRU has linked&lt;/a&gt;
 on their home website that we thought was too clunky and cluttered for people who are new to the campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe CasePlace is an improvement over this webpage due to the sorting functionality it offers. Newcomers to our campus are unlikely to know the names of buildings, or what they are even looking for. CasePlace simplifies this by allowing them to filter and sort the pinned locations into administrative buildings, restaurants, bus stops, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;design&#34;&gt;Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the design phase, we spent a lot of time working on wireframes in order to make sure we knew exactly what we wanted before starting program. For the purposes of wireframing we used Figma, which is like the Google Docs of wireframing. Here is an example of our very early drafts!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/casePlace/earlyWireframe.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once we had decided on a general layout, we began to focus more on the style and feel of our application. We thought it would be fitting to make our website match &lt;a href=&#34;https://case.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CWRU&amp;rsquo;s professional websites&lt;/a&gt;
 for continuity purposes as these websites all share the same audience. In order to emulate CWRU&amp;rsquo;s websites, we started by using their same color palette and fonts. We then moved on to making our CSS emulate features across CWRU&amp;rsquo;s websites for buttons, modals, dropdowns, etc. Here is one of our later design drafts!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/casePlace/hiResWireframe.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using CWRU&amp;rsquo;s map page as a model, we took our ideas from the design phase and got to work to make it happen. Here is a side by side comparison &amp;ndash; decide for yourself whether or not we matched CWRU&amp;rsquo;s feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;CasePlace&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;CWRU&amp;rsquo;s Page&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/casePlace/casePlace.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/casePlace/caseWebApp.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;technology&#34;&gt;Technology&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this project we used a variety of different languages and applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Framework: React (with CSS and HTML)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version Control: Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ticketing System: Jira&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design Tool: Figma&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Server Host: Digital Ocean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luckily for us, we were able to use Jira, Figma, and Digital Ocean for &lt;em&gt;FREE&lt;/em&gt; due to all of us being students!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was my first time using React and I really enjoyed using it. It strikes me as a (maybe a little &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt;) robust, but powerful framework. I&amp;rsquo;m no expert, but I think you could make just about any web-app you want using React.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;group-organization&#34;&gt;Group Organization&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since this was a multi-month long project, it was super important to us as a group that we stayed on top of our work and made steady progress throughout the semester. In order to adhere to this, we elected one of our members, Elias, as project manager for the semester. Elias was the perfect candidate since he had just worked as a project management intern for Google the previous Summer!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We started the semester by planning out our sprints and setting dates for certain deadlines. For instance, we allotted 1 week for setting up our environments, 3 weeks for design, and 2 weeks for debugging. We also all agreed to meet with one another twice a week to hold &amp;ldquo;scrum&amp;rdquo; meetings in which we would discuss the status of our project and what we were all working on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elias made is super easy for all us to keep track of our tasks due to his familiarity with Jira. For each sprint, he would make a new story and break it into sub-tasks to be distributed amongst us in the group. As a result of how organized we were, we ended up ahead of schedule by the end of the semester while many groups were cramming to get their projects working.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-contributions&#34;&gt;My Contributions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, I worked with 5 amazing people and didn&amp;rsquo;t have to deal with people not pulling their own weight. We were an extremely cohesive group who were all committed to working on this project as if it were a professional task for a client rather than a professor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally worked on almost all aspects of the project, but I am especially proud of what I managed to accomplish during the design phase. While using Figma, I had the realization that I really enjoyed the challenge of designing a page that was both intuitive AND aesthetic. This pushed me to take the lead on a number of things during the design phase, such as the CSS used for our components.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the development phase I worked on both the front-end and back-end. For instance, one of my subtasks was to implement the tooltips that open when a user clicks on one of the pins on our map. This required me to write logic for an action handler in JSX that would trigger a new HTML component to appear that I styled in CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/casePlace/tooltip.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; You do not want to know how long I spent trying to get the tooltip to have that tiny little triangle at the top!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned&#34;&gt;Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The success of our project was entirely due to our organization. From working on CasePlace I learned how valuable an agile development cycle can be, and how the structure it offers helps everyone on the team stay on task. Furthermore, without a good project manager and a clear division of labor (i.e. Jira) it would have been much, &lt;em&gt;much&lt;/em&gt; more difficult for us to work together effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>passwordManager</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/petprojects/passwordmanager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 14:14:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/petprojects/passwordmanager/</guid>
      <description>Intro After learning about the risks of reusing passwords I realized that I was in trouble. For the sake of convenience, I used to use one of a handful of passwords for all of my account logins (who the heck can remember a unique password for every single login!?) which makes me particularly susceptible to hacks. A big wakeup call for me was the LinkedIn hack in which thousands of users had their username and passwords stolen.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After learning about the &lt;a href=&#34;https://privacysavvy.com/password/guides/reusing-passwords/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;risks of reusing passwords&lt;/a&gt;
 I realized that I was in trouble. For the sake of convenience, I used to use one of a handful of passwords for all of my account logins (who the heck can remember a unique password for every single login!?) which makes me particularly susceptible to hacks. A big wakeup call for me was the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forbes.com/sites/leemathews/2021/06/29/details-on-700-million-linkedin-users-for-sale-on-notorious-hacking-forum/?sh=6c337b3234a4&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;LinkedIn hack&lt;/a&gt;
 in which thousands of users had their username and passwords stolen. I had no way of knowing whether my information had been compromised or not, but if it had someone could see my LinkedIn password and use that to access another dozen of my accounts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This freaked me out and spurred me to take action. I decided that it was time I come up with a way of safely storing my login information, and I started work on my own password manager.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out the source code on my &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/camfarms/SecureLoginPHP&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;github&lt;/a&gt;
!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;demo&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out my demo on my YouTube channel

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6MwuE5ZzHd8&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-method&#34;&gt;The Method&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When starting this project my two main considerations were &lt;strong&gt;convenience and security&lt;/strong&gt;. How could I protect my login profiles from prying eyes, while still making it easily accessible? After some brainstorming, I decided that I wanted to keep all of my passwords locally on my machine for ease-of-access, but didn&amp;rsquo;t want them stored in plain text in case anyone got into my computer and could read my files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to make this possible, I needed some way to &lt;strong&gt;encrypt&lt;/strong&gt; my login information before saving it locally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;encryption&#34;&gt;Encryption&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t know much about encryption, so I started doing some research and found a method that would serve my purposes. I won&amp;rsquo;t go too deeply into detail on the encryption, but here&amp;rsquo;s the gist:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Given a &lt;strong&gt;key&lt;/strong&gt;, the algorithm will encode a given string, converting it into a long nonsense-looking sequence of characters called a &lt;strong&gt;cipher text&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any &lt;strong&gt;cipher text&lt;/strong&gt; generated by this algorithm can be decoded and converted back to the original string as long as the same &lt;strong&gt;key&lt;/strong&gt; is provided to do the decoding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-interface&#34;&gt;The Interface&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once I had determined my method of security I got to work on making a convenient implementation. For the sake of simplicity, I decided to make my password manager a script that I could run from terminal. At the time, I had been using PHP for one of my classes and decided it was the language for the job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To use my terminal based password manager, you must first enter a &lt;strong&gt;cryptographic key&lt;/strong&gt;. From then on, that cryptographic key is used for all encoding/decoding for the rest of the session. You are able to navigate through the different menus of the script by entering commands into the command line. Here&amp;rsquo;s what it looks like when you first start it up:

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/passManager/passManagerUsage.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-code&#34;&gt;The Code&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the code behind that beautiful starting menu:



  &lt;div class=&#34;collapsable-code&#34;&gt;
    &lt;input id=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34; checked /&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;1&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__language&#34;&gt;php&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__title&#34;&gt;Script&amp;rsquo;s usage menu&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__toggle&#34; data-label-expand=&#34;Show&#34; data-label-collapse=&#34;Hide&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;pre class=&#34;language-php&#34; &gt;&lt;code&gt;
function usage(){
	echo &amp;#34;\033[92mUsage: Type a command below to begin
		exit   ........................................  exit this script
		list   ........................................  list all saved login profiles
		add, [OPTIONAL NAME] ..........................  create a new profile, and save its encrypted login information		
		del, [OPTIONAL NAME] ..........................  delete an existing password
		look,  [OPTIONAL NAME] ........................  lookup the plaintext username and password of a profile
		update, [OPTIONAL NAME] .......................  update a profile&amp;#39;s name, and plaintext username and password
			\033[39m\n\n&amp;#34;;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The script works by continually waiting for input commands. Each valid command (i.e. exit, list, etc.) has its own PHP class that implements an interface called &lt;strong&gt;Command&lt;/strong&gt;.
Here is the command interface, and the &lt;strong&gt;$exit&lt;/strong&gt; class overwriting the interface&amp;rsquo;s functions:



  &lt;div class=&#34;collapsable-code&#34;&gt;
    &lt;input id=&#34;2&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34; checked /&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__language&#34;&gt;php&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__title&#34;&gt;Command interface and $exit class&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__toggle&#34; data-label-expand=&#34;Show&#34; data-label-collapse=&#34;Hide&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;pre class=&#34;language-php&#34; &gt;&lt;code&gt;
interface Command{
	public function execute($args);
	public function isValid($args);
	public function help();
	public function error();
}

$exit = new class implements Command{
	public function execute($args){
		global $handle;
		echo &amp;#34;Exiting...&amp;#34;;
		fclose($handle);
		exit;
	}

	public function isValid($args){
		return count($args) == 1;
	}

	public function help(){
		echo &amp;#34;exit - exits the program. Accepts no arguments\n&amp;#34;;
	}

	public function error(){
		echo &amp;#34;\033[91mERROR: Invalid exit command syntax\n&amp;#34;;
		echo &amp;#34;\033[39m&amp;#34;;
	}
};
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once a string is entered by the user, it is first checked to make sure it is a valid command. If it is, the class &lt;strong&gt;execute($args)&lt;/strong&gt; function for that command is called. Here is the input loop:



  &lt;div class=&#34;collapsable-code&#34;&gt;
    &lt;input id=&#34;3&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34; checked /&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__language&#34;&gt;php&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__title&#34;&gt;Input loop&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__toggle&#34; data-label-expand=&#34;Show&#34; data-label-collapse=&#34;Hide&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;pre class=&#34;language-php&#34; &gt;&lt;code&gt;
//Map of acceptable commands 
$commands = array(&amp;#34;exit&amp;#34; =&amp;gt; $exit, &amp;#34;list&amp;#34; =&amp;gt; $list, &amp;#34;add&amp;#34; =&amp;gt; $add, &amp;#34;del&amp;#34; =&amp;gt; $del, &amp;#34;look&amp;#34; =&amp;gt; $look, &amp;#34;update&amp;#34; =&amp;gt; $update);

//Open standard in
$handle = fopen (&amp;#34;php://stdin&amp;#34;,&amp;#34;r&amp;#34;);
echo &amp;#34;Enter cryptographic key to encode and decode passwords:\n&amp;#34;;
$key = trim(fgets($handle));
usage();

//user input loop
while(true){
	$in = trim(fgets($handle));
	$args = explode(&amp;#39;,&amp;#39;, $in);
	$command = $args[0];

	if (in_array($command, array_keys($commands))) {
		if($commands[$command]-&amp;gt;isValid($args)){
			$commands[$command]-&amp;gt;execute($args);
		}
		else{
			$commands[$command]-&amp;gt; error();
			$commands[$command]-&amp;gt;help();
			mainmenu();

		}
	}	
	else{
		echo &amp;#34;\033[91mERROR: Not a valid command.\n&amp;#34;;
		mainmenu();
	}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;screenshots&#34;&gt;Screenshots&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see the saved login profiles, you use the &lt;strong&gt;list&lt;/strong&gt; command.

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/passManager/passManagerList.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

In order to view the login profile&amp;rsquo;s plaintext username and password, you use the &lt;strong&gt;look&lt;/strong&gt; command. If you entered the cryptographic key used to encode the profile when entering the session, the profile will be decoded and printed out for you to view. Since &lt;strong&gt;I did not use the same crpytographic key&lt;/strong&gt; when starting this session, the login progile will not be decoded for me to view:

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/passManager/passManagerLook.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

If you wanted to create a new login profile, you use the &lt;strong&gt;add&lt;/strong&gt; command. The user is first prompted to enter a name for a profile, and then enter the plaintext username and password for the profile. The user also has the option to have a password randomly generated for them!
Now, when the &lt;strong&gt;look&lt;/strong&gt; command is used on the new profile, its plaintext username and password is given since it was encoded using the &lt;strong&gt;same cryptographic key&lt;/strong&gt;.

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/passManager/passManagerAdd.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-textfile&#34;&gt;The Textfile&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This script utilizes a textfile to save the encrypted profile information. Both the usernames and passwords are encrypted before being written to the file, and they are read in their encrypted form into the script when being looked up. Here is what the textfile looks like with its encrypted information:

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/passManager/encryptedProfiles.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>solutionStreet</title>
      <link>/workxp/softdevinternships/solutionstreet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 15:47:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workxp/softdevinternships/solutionstreet/</guid>
      <description>Intro Following my Freshman year at Case Wester Reserve University, I was hired as an intern for a local software development company called Solution Street. At Solution Street I had the opportunity to work with a team entirely composed of interns (except for our team lead) on an entirely new project! This presented a unique learning opportunity and taught me so much more about software development beyond the technical details.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following my Freshman year at Case Wester Reserve University, I was hired as an intern for a local software development company called Solution Street. At Solution Street I had the opportunity to work with a team entirely composed of interns (except for our team lead) on an entirely new project! This presented a unique learning opportunity and taught me so much more about software development beyond the technical details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a team, we were tasked with creating a new web-based application for a local catering company &amp;ndash; Smokin&#39; Willy&amp;rsquo;s BBQ! The owner of Smokin&#39; Willy&amp;rsquo;s was having trouble managing a increasing number of orders and came to Solution Street looking for a business solution. A deal was struck between the two and a team of 4 interns and 1 part-time employee got to work on an application in exchange for free catering at future company picnics!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;meet-the-team&#34;&gt;Meet the Team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I worked with 3 other interns at Solution Street named Greg, Mark, and Adam. We were led by a part time employee named Olga Lorenz &amp;ndash; she&amp;rsquo;s awesome. The 5 of us all reported to Arthur Frankel, a co-founder of Solution Street (and the guy in charge of hiring us).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Arthur&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Olga&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/workXp/arthur.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/workXp/olga.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;Co-founder of Solution Street, and who hired me!&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:center&#34;&gt;My team leader&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-contributions&#34;&gt;My Contributions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a team, we sat down with the owner of Smokin&#39; Willy&amp;rsquo;s (the William himself!) and worked with him to understand his business practices and what we could do to make running his business easier. Olga would lead these meetings, but all of us made suggestions and contributed to the discussion of what we could build for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once we had an idea of how his business worked, we got to work on development. We followed an Agile development cycle which consisted of daily scrum meetings and weekly sprint meetings &amp;ndash; which William was present for. We used Unfuddle as our ticketing system, and under Olga&amp;rsquo;s guidance we began to build the web application using a Ruby on Rails back-end and an HTML/CSS front end. We often worked together on the same tickets since we were all seated next to each other in the office, and we made code peer reviews a normal practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a developer I worked on a number of different parts of the web application, both front-end and back-end. One of the features I am most proud of is a calendar embedded in the home page of the website. This calendar was dynamic and would automatically be populated with orders as they came in through the website! When clicked on, events could be added to the calendar and existing events could be expanded or modified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned&#34;&gt;Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since Solution Street was my first serious software development position, I learned a ton about the development process and technology. It was my first exposure to an agile development cycle and a full stack framework such as Ruby on Rails. This helped me become a much more technically proficient candidate for future internship positions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond the technical side of software development, however, I also learned about the business side. Being able to sit down and talk face-to-face with a client was an extremely rewarding experience and it greatly expanded my understanding of how software development companies do business. Something that struck me was the importance of communication between the developers and the client, and how there can often be a bit of a &amp;ldquo;language barrier&amp;rdquo; between the two. For instance, William was an excellent chef but he didn&amp;rsquo;t know anything about software; it became our job as representatives of Solution Street to help him understand the potential of our application.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The way we did this was by first asking him to explain to us his normal business process for taking and filling orders. This gave us a general picture for what kind of application to make. Then, we asked that he identify the steps in his business process that took the most time and together we discussed how we could build off the current application to automate those time consuming steps. Sitting down and working with a client taught me so much about software development that I had never considered before and encouraged me to view the industry more from the view of the consumer than the producer.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weightLifting</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/hobbies/weightlifting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 12:34:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/hobbies/weightlifting/</guid>
      <description>Intro Physical fitness has always been extremely important to me. Without constant exercise, I start to go stir crazy and get super irritable. This was never a problem in high school when I was playing a variety of sports and had daily practices, but since graduating and moving on to college I needed to find a new outlet. Several of my close friends in high school took up weight lifting and they introduced me to it the Summer after my Freshman year &amp;ndash; I quickly took to it and dived in head first after two semesters of restlessness.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Physical fitness has always been extremely important to me. Without constant exercise, I start to go stir crazy and get super irritable. This was never a problem in high school when I was playing  a variety of sports and had daily practices, but since graduating and moving on to college I needed to find a new outlet. Several of my close friends in high school took up weight lifting and they introduced me to it the Summer after my Freshman year &amp;ndash; I quickly took to it and dived in head first after two semesters of restlessness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lifting appeals to me greatly because it is very flexible. Depending on what else I have going on in my lift, I can make lifting as rigorous or relaxed as I like. It also has tons of variation to it so I&amp;rsquo;ll never get bored with it &amp;ndash; if I get tired to doing some exercises I&amp;rsquo;ll just write a new split and start working on other stuff!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The empirical nature of it also appeals to me &amp;ndash; it is extremely easy to measure and track progress which makes setting goals easy. I joke sometimes that lifting is like real life Runescape, but instead of getting experience for a profession you&amp;rsquo;re just getting a high max score for certain lifts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;diet&#34;&gt;Diet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have learned that diet is the number one most important thing when lifting &lt;em&gt;BY FAR&lt;/em&gt;. I would go so far as to say 80% diet : 20 % working out. This is because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter what you&amp;rsquo;re doing in the gym &amp;ndash; if you aren&amp;rsquo;t eating right, you won&amp;rsquo;t build muscle. Without fuel, your body simply can&amp;rsquo;t build muscle or replenish itself!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a tough lesson for me to learn since I have had a problem with under-eating since I was a kid. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until I started forcing myself to eat more that I finally started to see rapid progress towards my goals in the gym. It took me a while to figure out how much my body needed, but I now know my body&amp;rsquo;s baseline is ~1670-1700 daily calories to maintain my current weight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When attempting to gain muscle, you &lt;em&gt;MUST&lt;/em&gt; hit your body&amp;rsquo;s baseline calorie count each day. The fact of the matter is, its impossible to gain &lt;em&gt;ANYTHING &amp;ndash; fat or muscle&lt;/em&gt; unless you are eating a caloric surplus. Generally, it is recommended you try to eat a surplus of 500 calories on exercise days if you want to gain ~1 lb per week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-current-split&#34;&gt;My Current Split&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the fall semester of 2021 I have had a lot of time to focus on lifting due to my academic load being relatively light. As a result, I have taken this opportunity to put on as much muscle as possible before I get busy again. This is because it is relatively easy to maintain muscle mass compared to building it (since building muscle requires much high regularity of eating and exercising).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This semester I have had the ambitious goal of exercising 6 days a week, and eating 2200+ calories each day. This dietary part has been by far the more difficult of the two since I have such a bad habit of under eating. However, I have been able to put together weekly meals that help me reach my caloric goal. I have also set numeric goals for my sets in the gym:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comfortable 5x5 Weight:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bench Press: 185&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Squat: 225&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dead Lift: 225&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;split&#34;&gt;Split&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Goals:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthen chest and increase bench press weight.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5x5 @ 185, 3x2 @ 225&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build up core strength&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain barbell squat and practice technique&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6 Day Split: Push -&amp;gt; Pull -&amp;gt; Legs -&amp;gt; Push -&amp;gt; Pull -&amp;gt; Core&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Day&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Week Day&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Schedule&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Duration&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Push A&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Monday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Barbell Bench Press&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;1x Warmup, 2x 5-8 Heavy, 3x 10-12 Moderate&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Chest Fly x Tricep Extension (Super Set)&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12, 4x 7-10&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Lateral Dumbbell Raise&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Shrugs&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Dips&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x AMRAP&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Pull A&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tuesday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Pull up&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x Warm up&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Hammer Curl&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Reverse Grip Rows&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Cable Curls&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Cable Rows&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x 20 Drop Set&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;6) Dumbbell Curls&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;1x Triple Drop Set&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Legs&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Wednesday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Box Jumps&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x Warm up&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Barbell Back Squat&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x Warm up, 4x 8-12 Heavy, 1x AMRAP Moderate&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Barbell Standing Calf Raise&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12 (then paritals until failure)&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Hip Thrusts&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Quad Extensions&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x 10-12, 2x Triple Drop Set&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;90m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Push B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Thursday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Standing Overhead Barbell Press&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Incline Dumbbell Press x Push up (Super Set)&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Overhead Tricep Extension&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Cable or Machine Fly&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Dips&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x AMRAP&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;60m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Pull B&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Friday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Lat Pulldown&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x Warm up, 3x 8-10 Drop set&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Dumbbell Row&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x Warm up, 2x 6-8 Heavy, 1x 10-12 Moderate&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Incline Seated Dumbbell Curls&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 10-12&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Pull Up&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x AMRAP&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Reverse EZ Bar Curl&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;2x 8-10, 2x 40 seconds&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Core&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Saturday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;1) Medicine Ball Twist&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 20&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;2) Crunches w Twist&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;4x 20&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;3) Ab Roll-out x Hanging Knee Raises (Super Set)&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;3x 15&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;4) Good Morning&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;5x 15&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;5) Plank&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;1x Through the Fire and the Flames track&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;75m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;REST&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sunday&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Yoga/Stretching&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;30m&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>movieWatchList</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/hobbies/moviewatchlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 20:17:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/hobbies/moviewatchlist/</guid>
      <description>Intro I have absolutely loved film ever since I made friends with Ethan M. in high school. He exposed me to all sorts of fantastic movies and opened my eyes to the awesome potential the cinema has for art and storytelling. Since high school I have delved deeper and deeper into my love of film by taking film classes and watching movies often. I always have an ongoing watch list (see below) of movies, but it has always been my preference to see movies in theaters.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have absolutely loved film ever since I made friends with Ethan M. in high school. He exposed me to all sorts of fantastic movies and opened my eyes to the awesome potential the cinema has for art and storytelling. Since high school I have delved deeper and deeper into my love of film by taking film classes and watching movies often. I always have an ongoing watch list (see below) of movies, but it has always been my preference to see movies in theaters. On this page I will keep my watch list as well as keep track of movies I have seen in theaters that were exceptional. I hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;favorite-theater-viewings&#34;&gt;Favorite Theater Viewings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally think there are some movies that can only be fully enjoyed when seen in theaters &amp;ndash; &lt;em&gt;Pacific Rim&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Saving Private Ryan&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt;, etc. The movie theater is the original medium of film and immerses the audience unlike any home theater could with the larger-than-life screen and the seat shaking speakers. Since many people would disagree with me on this, I have decided to compile a list of the movies I have seen in theaters that I felt were &lt;em&gt;enhanced&lt;/em&gt; by the venue itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;9302021---akira&#34;&gt;9/30/2021 - Akira&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Akira at the time of its release (1988) had the highest budget of any animated movie up until that point, and it shows. Entirely hand drawn, the film has a run time of 124 minutes which required over an estimated 160,000 individual drawings. This makes for a wonderfully fluid and smooth viewing experience which became the inspiration for an entire generation of Japanese media.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/movieWatchList/akira.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The movie takes you through a Neo-Tokyo cityscape plagued by corruption, gang violence, and terrorism as the main character, Kaneda, searches for his abducted friend Tetsuo. From the action shots to the world building, the animation is breathtaking and easily surpasses many of its modern copy-cats. The soundtrack is still infamous for its eerie undertones and perfectly sets the mood. But, don&amp;rsquo;t take my word for it, watch the introduction for yourself! (there are English captions)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Avnq3rFnezE&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, enough gushing. I had the opportunity to see the remastered &lt;em&gt;Akira&lt;/em&gt; with its original audio in theaters while at school and I eagerly jumped at the chance. I went with several of my friends (some seeing it for the first time) and we all walked out as if in a daze &amp;ndash; it was awesome! If you ever get the chance to see it in theaters DO SO! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t had the chance to see it yet, WATCH IT!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: Only watch &lt;em&gt;Akira&lt;/em&gt; if you can see it in its original audio version with subtitles; the &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/ve-SiqRYLXM&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;English dub is absolutely terrible&lt;/a&gt;
 and breaks the spell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;10282021---dune&#34;&gt;10/28/2021 - Dune&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soon after its release, I made a point of making a trip to a movie theater to see some sandworms on the big screen. I read &lt;em&gt;Dune&lt;/em&gt; over quarantine in 2020 and absolutely loved it, prompting me to read the next 3 books in the series. When I heard there was a movie coming out, and directed by Denis Villeneuve nonetheless, I could barely contain my excitement. However, I had been disappointed by movies portrayals of books before so I tried to temper my enthusiasm&amp;hellip; but I was almost entirely unsuccessful.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/movieWatchList/dune.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily, there was no need to curb my enthusiasm because &lt;em&gt;Dune&lt;/em&gt; exceeded my expectations in terms of cinematic aesthetic while still adhering strongly to the book&amp;rsquo;s plot. I thought the soundtrack was wonderfully fitting and the entire atmosphere of the movie practically screamed &amp;ldquo;Arrakis!&amp;rdquo;. Cinematically the world building was wonderful and the culture and technology on display carried an undeniable &lt;em&gt;weight&lt;/em&gt; to it &amp;ndash; I should have expected no less of the director of &lt;em&gt;Arrival&lt;/em&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The big screen only helped to enhance the beautiful landscapes and civilizations built within the camera&amp;rsquo;s lens. I think I will be making a return trip to the theater soon before it&amp;rsquo;s too late to see it again&amp;hellip; maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll do IMAX this time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-watch-list&#34;&gt;My Watch List&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Title&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Genre&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Amadeus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Come and See&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dallas Buyers Club&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Do the Right Thing&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, Comedy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Driveways&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Knife in the Water&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama, Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Green Mile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;A Promising Young Woman&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Girl with the Dragon Tattoo&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense, Mystery&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Assistant&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Gift&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Touching the Void&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;A Ghost Story&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Moonstruck&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Witness&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Romance, Crime&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Upgrade&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Action&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chronicle&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Action&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;High Life&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Suspense&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sputnik&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tenet&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Road&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sci-Fi, Post Apocalyptic&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Dr. Stangelove&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Comedy, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Napoleon Dynamite&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Comedy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Citizen 4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Crumb&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Last Breath&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, Horror&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;This is What Winning Looks Like&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Documentary, War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Jarhead&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Schindler&amp;rsquo;s List&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Deer Hunter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;The Manchurian Candidate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;War&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Clue (1985)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Mystery&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Winter Bones&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Mystery, Drama&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Rango&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Western&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Blue Velvet&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Thriller&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>raspPiMediaHub (WIP)</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/petprojects/rasppimediahub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 14:42:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/petprojects/rasppimediahub/</guid>
      <description>Intro I am a huge movie and TV show buff which means I spend a lot of time with my laptop hooked up to my TV via and HDMI cord. However, constantly having to plug and unplug my sole laptop into the TV has gotten annoying&amp;hellip; so I present to you the Raspberry Pi Media Center!
It is my hope that this will be able to replace my laptop as a designated streaming box for any and all media I want to access.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a huge movie and TV show buff which means I spend a lot of time with my laptop hooked up to my TV via and HDMI cord. However, constantly having to plug and unplug my sole laptop into the TV has gotten annoying&amp;hellip; so I present to you the Raspberry Pi Media Center!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is my hope that this will be able to replace my laptop as a designated streaming box for any and all media I want to access. Fortunately, I have most streaming platforms and can easily rent movies through Amazon. Assuming I can get the Pi up and running, I will soon never have to worry about forgetting my laptop and home again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-parts&#34;&gt;The Parts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From my research for this project I decided that I would use &lt;a href=&#34;https://osmc.tv&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;OSMC&lt;/a&gt;
 and a Raspberry Pi 4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The choice to use OSMC was a relatively simple one. The first benefit of using OSMC is its extremely easy installation, and the second is its vibrant and active community supporting it. It is an extremely popular Pi OS, and has established itself in the community of fellow Pi heads. It also does exactly what I want it to do &amp;ndash; it mimics a media center with its own app installer and tile interface! One drawback however, is its a rather robust Pi OS (which maybe isn&amp;rsquo;t even a bad thing?) which makes it pretty cumbersome and difficult to configure or personalize. But, for my first foray into the realm of the Raspberry Pi I&amp;rsquo;m content to keep my training wheels on &amp;ndash; even if it isn&amp;rsquo;t a super lightweight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I quickly determined that a B or B+ model board would be best for me due to its ethernet port (a &lt;strong&gt;MUST&lt;/strong&gt; in my opinion), HDMI/Micro-HDMI ports, and widespread use amongst people making media hubs. After learning more about the available hardware I was deciding between the Pi 3 and Pi 4 boards. The Pi 4, while being more expensive, outpaces the Pi 3 in almost every benchmark &lt;em&gt;BUT&lt;/em&gt; is extremely hard to find in its B+ configuration due to its recent release. But, since I haven&amp;rsquo;t used a Pi before and don&amp;rsquo;t know what exactly the demand would be on the hardware, I decided to opt for the safer option and splurged on the Pi 4 B model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To complement my purchase I also bought an SD card for installing the OS, a micro-HDMI to HDMI adapter, and a cute little plastic case to keep it all safe.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;/img/raspPiMediaHub/pi4B.png&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;Raspberry Pi 4 B&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The parts are due to arrive this week, I can&amp;rsquo;t wait!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>caseFunFinder</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/schoolwork/casefunfinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 13:31:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/schoolwork/casefunfinder/</guid>
      <description>Intro Intro to Databases was one of my favorite classes during my Senior year of undergrad. During the course I learnt so much about the theory behind database structures and organization which instilled in me an appreciation how our information is stored. Databases pose their own unique problems and require elegant (and often mathematically provable) solutions. This made the class extremely exciting to me and I had a lot of fun working on the final project.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intro to Databases was one of my favorite classes during my Senior year of undergrad. During the course I learnt so much about the theory behind database structures and organization which instilled in me an appreciation how our information is stored. Databases pose their own unique problems and require elegant (and often mathematically provable) solutions. This made the class extremely exciting to me and I had a lot of fun working on the final project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My group and I decided to make CaseFunFinder &amp;ndash; a simple application that interfaced with a database of geographical attractions around our school (Case Western Reserve University). We started our project with a design phase during which we came up with a structure for organizing the type of information we wanted to store. Once we had decided on the arrangement of our data, we used SQL to create and populate our database&amp;rsquo;s tables. Then, we connected the database to a very basic React site we were running on localhost in order to demo our project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;demo&#34;&gt;Demo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the demo of our database! (Thanks Randall &amp;lt;3)

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/osVOPDL2Vms&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;design&#34;&gt;Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of our database was to store information relevant to locations around our university and the greater Cleveland area. This posed a unique problem for us and necessitated that we come up with a clever way to organize our data. After considering a variety of solutions, we decided the most elegant way to structure our data was to categorize the locations we wanted to capture. We deliberated and elected to categorize all of our attractions into one of four groups: parks, museums/historical landmarks, theaters/performing art centers, and restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By categorizing all of our location data, we were able to create an &lt;strong&gt;is-a&lt;/strong&gt; relationship within our database. That is, we created a table for each category, as well as a table with every single attraction across all categories called &lt;strong&gt;Attractions&lt;/strong&gt;. That table contained general information attractions such as its name, address, opening time, and so on.  This enabled us to store more information specific to each category within their own respective tables &amp;ndash; for instance, each restaurant has a field for whether or not it has vegetarian options!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each attraction also has a field called its &lt;strong&gt;fun id&lt;/strong&gt;, which acts as its unique identifier. The &lt;strong&gt;fun id&lt;/strong&gt; is used as a primary key and is necessary to utilize the aforementioned is-a relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;/img/caseFunFinder/erDiagram.png&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;ER Diagram for our database&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our database did not stop at just attractions, however. Since it was meant to be used as part of a larger application we included a table for user information. The user table was used to store information such as the user&amp;rsquo;s name, and login information as well as a &lt;strong&gt;user id&lt;/strong&gt; which acted as a unique identifier for each user. This allowed us to expand the capability of our database when we realized we could make a relationship between users and events! This lead us to the creation of the &lt;strong&gt;Is tracking&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Is favorite&lt;/strong&gt; relationship tables which contain entries composed of two primary keys: &lt;strong&gt;user id&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;fun id&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We really liked this idea of relationships between entities in different tables, we decided to take it a step further. We created an entirely new type of entity called an &lt;strong&gt;Event&lt;/strong&gt;! Events always take place at locations, so we used the structure we already had for &lt;strong&gt;attractions&lt;/strong&gt; and created a new relationship called &lt;strong&gt;Hosts&lt;/strong&gt;. Events have information such as start time and date, whether its child friendly, etc. as well as fields for event&amp;rsquo;s name AND the attraction acting as its venue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-code&#34;&gt;The Code&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We created this database using MySQL and MySQLWorkbench. Once we had decided on our structure, it was a simple matter of creating our tables and inserting into them. Here is how we created our attractions table:&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;div class=&#34;collapsable-code&#34;&gt;
    &lt;input id=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;  /&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;1&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__language&#34;&gt;sql&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__title&#34;&gt;Creation of attraction table&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__toggle&#34; data-label-expand=&#34;Show&#34; data-label-collapse=&#34;Hide&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;pre class=&#34;language-sql&#34; &gt;&lt;code&gt;
CREATE TABLE `attractions` (
  `fun_id` int NOT NULL,
  `attraction_name` varchar(50) NOT NULL,
  `attraction_type` varchar(30) DEFAULT NULL,
  `street_address` varchar(100) DEFAULT NULL,
  `city` varchar(30) DEFAULT NULL,
  `zip_code` int DEFAULT NULL,
  `opening_hour` int DEFAULT NULL,
  `closing_hour` int DEFAULT NULL,
  `rating` decimal(2,1) DEFAULT NULL,
  `mask_required` varchar(1) DEFAULT NULL,
  PRIMARY KEY (`fun_id`,`attraction_name`)
) 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Here is how we made tables that were part of an &lt;strong&gt;is-a&lt;/strong&gt; relationship with attractions. Notice the &lt;strong&gt;REFERENCES&lt;/strong&gt; field:&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;div class=&#34;collapsable-code&#34;&gt;
    &lt;input id=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;  /&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;1&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__language&#34;&gt;sql&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__title&#34;&gt;Creation of restaurants table&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__toggle&#34; data-label-expand=&#34;Show&#34; data-label-collapse=&#34;Hide&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;pre class=&#34;language-sql&#34; &gt;&lt;code&gt;
CREATE TABLE `restaurants` (
  `fun_id` int NOT NULL,
  `rname` varchar(50) NOT NULL,
  `owner` varchar(50) DEFAULT NULL,
  `capacity_limit` varchar(10) DEFAULT NULL,
  `vegetarian_options` varchar(1) DEFAULT NULL,
  `vegan_options` varchar(1) DEFAULT NULL,
  PRIMARY KEY (`fun_id`,`rname`),
  KEY `fun_id_idx` (`fun_id`,`rname`),
  CONSTRAINT `fun_id, rname` FOREIGN KEY (`fun_id`, `rname`) REFERENCES `attractions` (`fun_id`, `attraction_name`) ON DELETE CASCADE ON UPDATE CASCADE
) 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;And finally, here is how we made relationships between tables. Notice how the only fields for any given entity are the primary keys of the tables it is relating:&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;div class=&#34;collapsable-code&#34;&gt;
    &lt;input id=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;  /&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;1&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__language&#34;&gt;sql&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__title&#34;&gt;Creation of is_tracking table&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__toggle&#34; data-label-expand=&#34;Show&#34; data-label-collapse=&#34;Hide&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;pre class=&#34;language-sql&#34; &gt;&lt;code&gt;
CREATE TABLE `is_tracking` (
  `cwru_id` varchar(30) NOT NULL,
  `fun_id` int NOT NULL,
  `attraction_name` varchar(50) DEFAULT NULL,
  PRIMARY KEY (`cwru_id`,`fun_id`),
  KEY `cwru_id_idx` (`cwru_id`),
  KEY `attraction_fun_id, attraction_name_idx` (`fun_id`,`attraction_name`),
  CONSTRAINT `attraction_fun_id, attraction_name` FOREIGN KEY (`fun_id`, `attraction_name`) REFERENCES `attractions` (`fun_id`, `attraction_name`) ON DELETE RESTRICT ON UPDATE RESTRICT,
  CONSTRAINT `cwru_id` FOREIGN KEY (`cwru_id`) REFERENCES `users` (`cwru_id`) ON DELETE RESTRICT ON UPDATE RESTRICT
)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The relationship tables posed a lot of problems due to the number of constraints they required. It took us a while to finally figure out how to create the table properly with all of the necessary checks in place. Furthermore, the entities in this table had to reference fields in other tables, which lead to a couple of bugs due to typos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-contributions&#34;&gt;My Contributions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really enjoyed the design phase of this project. I contributed greatly to the &lt;strong&gt;is-a&lt;/strong&gt; relationship structure of our projects, and suggested the categorizing of attractions. Once we reached development, we all worked together to get it working, but I am particularly proud of some of the more complex queries I came up with for our demo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For instance, check out this query:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;For each zip code, the user wants to find the attraction names and fun ids of attractions that host the maximum number of events; they then want the zip code, fun id, and attraction name of each such attraction listed.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;



  &lt;div class=&#34;collapsable-code&#34;&gt;
    &lt;input id=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;  /&gt;
    &lt;label for=&#34;1&#34;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__language&#34;&gt;sql&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__title&#34;&gt;Query for above request&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;collapsable-code__toggle&#34; data-label-expand=&#34;Show&#34; data-label-collapse=&#34;Hide&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/label&gt;
    &lt;pre class=&#34;language-sql&#34; &gt;&lt;code&gt;
WITH 	event_count(zip_code, host_fun_id, attraction_name, ct)
		(SELECT 	A2.zip_code, H2.host_fun_id, A2.attraction_name, COUNT(DISTINCT  H2.event_being_hosted_fun_id)
        FROM 		attractions A2, Hosts H2
		WHERE 	A2.fun_id = H2.host_fun_id
		GROUP BY 	A2.zip_code, H2.host_fun_id, A2.attraction_name),
SELECT 	A1.zip_code, A1.fun_id, A1.attraction_name
FROM 	attractions A1, event_count E
WHERE 	A1.fun_id = E.host_fun_id
AND 		E.ct = (SELECT MAX	(E2.ct)
	        		FROM 		event-count E2
	       		    WHERE 	A1.zip_code = E2.zip_code)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned&#34;&gt;Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am extremely appreciative of this class due to the value of learning how to write queries in SQL. I think our professor did an excellent job in training us to use all of SQL&amp;rsquo;s weird little features, and demanded that we compose complex queries for homework and tests very often. This made me very comfortable using SQL and MySQLWorkbench and has left me very confident in my ability to query a database.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, I also learned how to do a form of set mathematics that apply to databases in order to compose queries that are mathematically provably complete! I thought this was really cool since it was a direct connection between math and computer science I had never considered.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>italy2021 (WIP)</title>
      <link>/myportfolio/hobbies/traveling/italy2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 17:37:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/myportfolio/hobbies/traveling/italy2021/</guid>
      <description>Week 1 Jake and I touched down at the Venice Marco Polo Airport on August 15th after traveling for 18 hours from Washington D.C.&amp;rsquo;s Dulles Airport. Soon after landing, our friend Alessandro from Padova (a small city outside of Venice) picked us up in his tiny car. A 20 minute car ride later, we arrived at the Padova train station and picked up Rachel. The gang was finally all together!</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;week-1&#34;&gt;Week 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jake and I touched down at the Venice Marco Polo Airport on August 15th after traveling for 18 hours from Washington D.C.&amp;rsquo;s Dulles Airport. Soon after landing, our friend Alessandro from Padova (a small city outside of Venice) picked us up in his tiny car. A 20 minute car ride later, we arrived at the Padova train station and picked up Rachel. The gang was finally all together!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/theGang.png&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;(From left to right) Jake, Ale, Me and Rachel&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Needless to say, Jake and I were exhausted and SUPER jet lagged&amp;hellip; so that first day was a little rough and we ended up falling asleep while exploring Padova.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/jakeAsleep.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, day one was a bit of a wash. Oh well! But, we did get to sit down and have a lovely dinner (after a nap of course) with Ale&amp;rsquo;s Mom Sabrina!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/sabrina.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;verona&#34;&gt;Verona&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our first day trip was to the city of Verona, the home of Romeo and Juliet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
  div.gallery {
     display: flex;
     flex-wrap: wrap;
  }
        div.gallery a {
            flex-grow: 1;
            object-fit: cover;
            margin: 2px;
            display: flex;
        }

        div.gallery a img {            
            height: 200px;
            object-fit: cover;
            flex-grow: 1;
        }

    &lt;/style&gt;

    &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/fancybox/3.4.0/jquery.fancybox.min.css&#34; /&gt;

    &lt;div class=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;
        
	

	
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/verona//ale.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/verona//ale-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/verona//alejakerachel.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/verona//alejakerachel-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/verona//fermi.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/verona//fermi-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;52-galleries&#34;&gt;52 Galleries&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next on our list was a road trip to &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Strada_delle_52_Gallerie&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;52 galleries&lt;/a&gt;
 which is a series of 52 tunnels through the alps in Northern Italy. It is a historical site from WWI when it was used as a trail for munitions, but it also happens to be a beautiful hike! Joining us are Ale&amp;rsquo;s two high school friends Martina and Helena.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/theSquad.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
  div.gallery {
     display: flex;
     flex-wrap: wrap;
  }
        div.gallery a {
            flex-grow: 1;
            object-fit: cover;
            margin: 2px;
            display: flex;
        }

        div.gallery a img {            
            height: 200px;
            object-fit: cover;
            flex-grow: 1;
        }

    &lt;/style&gt;

    &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/fancybox/3.4.0/jquery.fancybox.min.css&#34; /&gt;

    &lt;div class=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;
        
	

	
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//donut.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//donut-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//jake.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//jake-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//start.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//start-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//trail.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//trail-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//trail2.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/52galleries//trail2-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;venice&#34;&gt;Venice&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being so close, we of course spent multiple days in Venice. Our first day we made no plans, and simply wandered around and explored the winding, narrow footpaths between buildings hundreds of years old. While in Venice we had tons of fun seeing historical landmarks, eating amazing food, and  drinking delicious (and cheap!) wine.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/grand.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
  div.gallery {
     display: flex;
     flex-wrap: wrap;
  }
        div.gallery a {
            flex-grow: 1;
            object-fit: cover;
            margin: 2px;
            display: flex;
        }

        div.gallery a img {            
            height: 200px;
            object-fit: cover;
            flex-grow: 1;
        }

    &lt;/style&gt;

    &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/fancybox/3.4.0/jquery.fancybox.min.css&#34; /&gt;

    &lt;div class=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;
        
	

	
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice//ale.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice//ale-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice//grandNight.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice//grandNight-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice//mask.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice//mask-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice//us3.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice//us3-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;murano-and-burano&#34;&gt;Murano and Burano&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Murano and Burano are two of the most famous Venetian islands which are known for their beautiful glasswork and colorful home fronts respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
  div.gallery {
     display: flex;
     flex-wrap: wrap;
  }
        div.gallery a {
            flex-grow: 1;
            object-fit: cover;
            margin: 2px;
            display: flex;
        }

        div.gallery a img {            
            height: 200px;
            object-fit: cover;
            flex-grow: 1;
        }

    &lt;/style&gt;

    &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/fancybox/3.4.0/jquery.fancybox.min.css&#34; /&gt;

    &lt;div class=&#34;gallery&#34;&gt;
        
	

	
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/ale.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/ale-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/boat.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/boat-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/burano.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/burano-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/eggs.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/eggs-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/fetus.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/fetus-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/jakenme.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/jakenme-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/lens.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/lens-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/rachel.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/rachel-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
	
            &lt;a data-fancybox=&#34;gallery&#34; href=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/sculpture.png&#34;&gt;
                &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/venice/murano_burano/sculpture-thumb.png&#34;&gt;  &lt;br/&gt;            
            &lt;/a&gt;
	
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;trip-to-the-beach&#34;&gt;Trip to the &amp;ldquo;Beach&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think there may have been something lost in translation with this one&amp;hellip; Ale told Jake and me that he was taking us to &amp;ldquo;the beach&amp;rdquo;, but what we infect went to was an &lt;em&gt;ice-cold mountain stream&lt;/em&gt; where people gather to go cliff jumping. But, regardless of the fact that I brought my volleyball, we still had an amazing time. Jake and I quickly worked our way up to the highest jump off points and started practicing our swan dives. Joining the three of us were Ale&amp;rsquo;s three friends Alcia, Helena, and Martina.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;/img/italy2021/week1/beach.png&#34;  class=&#34;left&#34;  /&gt;

</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aboutMe</title>
      <link>/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Hi there My name is Cameron Farmer, and I would like to tell you a little bit about myself! But before I do, here are some quick links to my resume and unofficial transcript .
(From left to right) Maddie, Emily, and Me at Emily&#39;s wedding  I am a soon-to-be graduate of Case Western Reserve of University with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s of Science in Computer Science. My professional interests lie within the realm of Software Development &amp;ndash; I am a maker, and I desire a future career that enables me to make bigger and better applications.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hi-there&#34;&gt;Hi there&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Cameron Farmer, and I would like to tell you a little bit about myself! But before I
do, here are some quick links to my &lt;a href=&#34;/CF_Resume_pdf.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;resume&lt;/a&gt;
 and &lt;a href=&#34;/unofficial_transcript.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;unofficial transcript&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;/img/about/emilyWedding.jpg&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;(From left to right) Maddie, Emily, and Me at Emily&#39;s wedding&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a soon-to-be graduate of Case Western Reserve of University with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s of Science in
Computer Science. My professional interests lie within the realm of Software Development &amp;ndash; I
am a maker, and I desire a future career that enables me to make bigger and better applications.
I also have a keen interest in the field of Artificial Intelligence, and will be seeking an
appropriate Master degree program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With my graduation approaching, I have been considering my post-graduation options and have come
up with two 5-year goals to give me some direction:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Live in another country&lt;/strong&gt; and learn the native language (assuming it&amp;rsquo;s not English)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earn a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in machine learning&lt;/strong&gt;, preferably in an international program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to achieve these goals, I have been applying to both professional and academic
opportunities across the globe in countries such as Israel and Germany. I have also been giving special consideration to international companies in hopes of starting work in the United States before requesting a transfer to a foreign office.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
