<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terminal</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 16:39:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>aboutMe</title>
      <link>/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Hi there My name is Cameron Farmer, and I would like to tell you a little bit about myself! But before I do, here are some quick links to my resume and unofficial transcript .
(From left to right) Maddie, Emily, and Me at Emily&#39;s wedding  I am a soon-to-be graduate of Case Western Reserve of University with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s of Science in Computer Science. My professional interests lie within the realm of Software Development &amp;ndash; I am a maker, and I desire a future career that enables me to make bigger and better applications.</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hi-there&#34;&gt;Hi there&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Cameron Farmer, and I would like to tell you a little bit about myself! But before I
do, here are some quick links to my &lt;a href=&#34;/CF_Resume_pdf.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;resume&lt;/a&gt;
 and &lt;a href=&#34;/unofficial_transcript.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;unofficial transcript&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;figure class=&#34;left&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;/img/about/emilyWedding.jpg&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;(From left to right) Maddie, Emily, and Me at Emily&#39;s wedding&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a soon-to-be graduate of Case Western Reserve of University with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s of Science in
Computer Science. My professional interests lie within the realm of Software Development &amp;ndash; I
am a maker, and I desire a future career that enables me to make bigger and better applications.
I also have a keen interest in the field of Artificial Intelligence, and will be seeking an
appropriate Master degree program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With my graduation approaching, I have been considering my post-graduation options and have come
up with two 5-year goals to give me some direction:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Live in another country&lt;/strong&gt; and learn the native language (assuming it&amp;rsquo;s not English)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Earn a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in AI&lt;/strong&gt;, preferably in an international program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to achieve these goals, I have been applying to both professional and academic
opportunities across the globe in countries such as Israel and Germany. I have also been giving special consideration to international companies in hopes of starting work in the United States before requesting a transfer to a foreign office.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
